
<Fenn>"I don't understand why someone would use some of this stuff,"</Fenn>

<Bethel>"Mortals are attracted to power,"</Bethel>

<Bethel>"The ones who tried to raid me were more attracted than most. Some of them were desperate, and many of these tools are the tools of desperation."</Bethel>

<Amaryllis>"Most of it will change shape to fit whoever wears it, at least to some extent, but I'm not sure that will work for Valencia."</Amaryllis>

<Juniper>"We're talking about cursed armor here,"</Juniper>

<Fenn>"Maybe let's not put random strangers into it?"</Fenn>

<Valencia>"Was any of this meant for me?"</Valencia>

<Bethel>"Meant for you?"</Bethel>

<Juniper>"The Dungeon Master nudges things sometimes,"</Juniper>

<Juniper>"He, uh, sets things up. Let's say there are a billion entads, most of them not great, right? Well, we've come across what, maybe two dozen so far? Much more, if you include all the ones that nominally belong to Amaryllis, or the ones that I've heard about in passing, and definitely if you include Uther's stuff. But of the ones that we actually have, or have interacted with, a hugely disproportionate number have been ones that I personally created, or which were used in the games that I played. It's proof of the Dungeon Master's thumb on the scale somewhere in the process."</Juniper>

<Bethel>"Ah,"</Bethel>

<Bethel>"So the thought is that this powerful entity sent people to their deaths inside of me because he foresaw that I would elect not to take them, that you would come to me, that I would choose not to kill you, and that Valencia would both be present in this party and live through her altercation at Headwater."</Bethel>

<Fenn>"Valencia is invincible,"</Fenn>

<Valencia>"Am not,"</Valencia>

<Fenn>"Are too,"</Fenn>

<Fenn>"I've never seen you take a hit. 'If you prick her, does she not bleed?' Well, no, because you're not going to be able to prick her, she'll dodge out of the way of the needle and then break your arm in two places."</Fenn>

<Valencia>"I said I was sorry,"</Valencia>

<Fenn>"Never said I was upset,"</Fenn>

<Amaryllis>"You swore a lot,"</Amaryllis>

<Amaryllis>"And then said that you were going to break her arm in her sleep."</Amaryllis>

<Fenn>"I say a lot of things,"</Fenn>

<Juniper>"Back to the matter at hand,"</Juniper>

<Juniper>"Yes, it's very possible that the Dungeon Master either foresaw everything and nudged it into the right configuration, or foresaw bits and pieces of things and set up a bunch of possibilities. Maybe … I mean, it's possible that each of these was intended for a different possible future, and the ones that seem obviously meant for Valencia are just because that's the timeline we ended up in, right?"</Juniper>

<Fenn>"I'm kind of over the existential stuff,"</Fenn>

<Fenn>"Bible study helped a lot with that."</Fenn>

<Amaryllis>"It's also possible that the Dungeon Master cheats more than he lets on,"</Amaryllis>

<Amaryllis>"He simply placed that armor there for Valencia a few days ago and retroactively altered all memories and evidence to fit a world where it had always been there."</Amaryllis>

<Juniper>"Sure,"</Juniper>

<Juniper>"If we're talking about random bullshit powers, yes, that's entirely possible."</Juniper>

<Bethel>"But it's to our benefit,"</Bethel>

<Valencia>"I'm going to try the armor on,"</Valencia>

<Juniper>"Sure,"</Juniper>

<Juniper>"We'll test it in the least harmful way possible."</Juniper>

<Amaryllis>"It's to our benefit now,"</Amaryllis>

<Amaryllis>"In the future? Maybe not so much. Also in the past, though it's hard to say."</Amaryllis>

<Fenn>"She's still salty about the password-protected tattoo variant,"</Fenn>

<Amaryllis>"Because it was bullshit,"</Amaryllis>

<Amaryllis>"The whole fucking thing, and yes, I'm still quote salty unquote about it. We were specifically fucked by a black swan."</Amaryllis>

<Fenn>"Like Leda,"</Fenn>

<Juniper>"Sometimes there are black swans,"</Juniper>

<Juniper>"I mean, you don't include them in narratives without some foreshadowing or multiple viewpoints, which basically means that you don't do them in tabletop games, but … I thought maybe that was the point?"</Juniper>

<Fenn>"The fuck kind of point is that?"</Fenn>

<Bethel>"I'm inclined to agree with the spirit of that question,"</Bethel>

<Amaryllis>"No, I understand it,"</Amaryllis>

<Amaryllis>"Fenn, did you ever get around to reading A Game of Thrones?"</Amaryllis>

<Fenn>"Nope,"</Fenn>

<Fenn>"If you wanted me to read books, you shouldn't have invented television."</Fenn>

<Amaryllis>"It's fine,"</Amaryllis>

<Amaryllis>"It was just a good example. Essentially, if you have a body of work built up, that engenders expectations, and in the context of an audience's reaction to narrative --"</Amaryllis>

<Fenn>"Snooze, pass, I'm done with it,"</Fenn>

<Fenn>"Look, I'm sorry if you find it interesting or worth spending time on, but unless it's actually going to help us in some way, I don't give a crap, and I don't think anyone else should either."</Fenn>

<Amaryllis>"Fine,"</Amaryllis>

<Amaryllis>"But you should know that it was a really interesting point."</Amaryllis>

<Fenn>"I'll put it on my internal scoreboard,"</Fenn>

<Juniper>"Is this how you two are when you're alone together?"</Juniper>

<Fenn>"Yes, exactly like that,"</Fenn>

<Fenn>"But usually we're naked and having a pillow fight while we talk."</Fenn>

<Valencia>"She does that with you too?"</Valencia>

<Amaryllis>"Are you using a devil to sell the joke?"</Amaryllis>

<Fenn>"Well, it was funny, I'll give you that,"</Fenn>

<Amaryllis>"You really need to stop doing that,"</Amaryllis>

<Amaryllis>"If they find out what's happening, and trace it back to you, they have methods of influencing Aerb. The hells haven't been united since the time of the Apocalypse Demon, and the dent Uther put in our cosmology has helped ensure only the weak can make it up, but trillions of infernals unified again isn't really something that we should risk for a joke."</Amaryllis>

<Valencia>"I'll just kill them all,"</Valencia>

<Valencia>"Jorge thinks that I should anyway."</Valencia>

<Fenn>"That sounds like exactly the sort of thing we should have a long talk about in the Council of Arches first,"</Fenn>

<Fenn>"I don't think we included a clause about genocide in the charter, but maybe we should have."</Fenn>

<Juniper>"I'm just saying, if there are a trillion people in the hells, which there might be, and they're being … I don't know, physically and psychologically tortured, then murdering all the devils and demons is probably the most possible good we can do, right?"